<archimate:ApplicationComponent
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    id="11c92975"
    name="Multiresource Scheduling"
    documentation="SAP Multiresource Scheduling provides separate master data that you can use to optimize the functions of SAP Multiresource Scheduling:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    Resource planning structure&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    The resource planning structure is a separate employee structure used for planning. It is independent of the HR organizational structure and allows you to assign resource planners, resources, contact persons, and work centers to resource planning nodes. However, you can also use the HR organizational plan as the resource planning structure.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    Qualifications, qualification catalogs, and qualification matrixes&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    As an alternative to using the standard HR qualifications, you can use SAP Multiresource Scheduling master data. This allows a more precise comparison of requirements and resources in order to determine the most suitable employees for tasks and vice versa. For the comparison, you can create combinations of qualifications from two different catalogs and enter a specific skill level in the profiles.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    Employee and requirements profiles&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    These combinations of qualifications and other criteria are the basis for comparison between the requirements of the task (the demand in the system) and the suitability of the employee for completing these tasks. You can select new profiles directly in the operations of orders and networks to create corresponding demands for resource planning.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    Transfer program for qualifications&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    If you do not want to create new master data but instead copy qualifications, qualification catalogs, and employee profiles from the standard system, you can use the relevant transfer programs (see Data Transfer).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    Roles and authorizations&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;    SAP Multiresource Scheduling authorizations allow you to specify who can edit qualification catalogs and matrixes, and when resources are to be displayed anonymously in the resource planning board, for example.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;http://help.sap.com/saphelp_mrs800_nw/helpdata/en/da/2decc6647f4ce29439f5c41df0f834/content.htm?frameset=/en/45/c1e4e6b98b47f2e10000000a114a6b/frameset.htm&amp;current_toc=/en/15/b399780a2b4c02be7f069c7525034c/plain.htm&amp;node_id=20&amp;show_children=false"/>
